<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Marc Alier (Ludo) - Home Page </title>
    <link>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Marc Alier (Ludo) - Home Page </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Marc Alier 2023. Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT: the good the bad and the Hallucinated</title>
      <link>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/posts/good_bad_alucinated/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/posts/good_bad_alucinated/</guid>
      <description>Table Of Contents AI-Generated Content Search Engine or Database Content Dealing with Hallucinations What Are Hallucinations? Hallucination Mitigation Strategies Practical strategies and use cases of Chatbots like ChatGTP Language Considerations: for best results, use English Putting Context i context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ai panic</title>
      <link>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/posts/ai-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/posts/ai-panic/</guid>
      <description>Found that on the former Twitter and I thought is was on point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A conversation with Martin Dougiamas about ICT and Education</title>
      <link>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wasabi.essi.upc.edu/ludo/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Martin Dougiamas is the creator of the Moodle open-source software project. I have collaborated with him extensively in the past. A few weeks ago, Martin was kind enough to come to visit me at LISA (Laboratori d&amp;rsquo;Inovació i Suport Audiovisual del ICE de la UPC) where we had a conversation for over an hour and a half about Education, Innovation, and many other things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
